This is Activa 6G, you can see and the
front panel in it has broken due to an accident,
you can see, there is a panel here,
this type of
panel has broken due to an accident and if
you do not want to get it fitted then how much does it cost from the company,
today I will tell you, we have
purchased it from a new company from Honda and
I will show you how much it costs,
this panel comes in packing like this, if we
talk about the price
then you can see
and the colour that comes in it is rough colour, it is
black colour but we have to get it painted,
this is a rub colour which costs ₹
300 to ₹400 or a glimpse of the colour, so
if you go to get the channel replaced then it will cost ₹1000
and if you get it painted then it will cost
₹1400 to 1300 and fitting
charges are charged separately, there will be a
fitting charge of around ₹100 to ₹150, so
if you want to get it changed then
you will have to pay around ₹1500  And
for such new videos, subscribe to our
YouTube channel. Thank you.